A Guide to the Near East Foundation records Accessions 2009.104, 2010.002, 2010.020 FA406
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2009.104: Near East Foundation records, 1915-2003; 1940-1980; AC 2009:104; 180 Cubic Feet 168 boxes, including 150 standard record storage boxes
  - Project Files
    - Iran Reports - Technicians Reports - General Corresp. regarding these Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 69)
      - NEF - Design for Ahwaz Agricultural College Site Plan, 2016:FA406:015 (Folder SF15)
    - Iran - Carl F. Kraenzel - Area Director - Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 69)
    - Iran - Reports - Technicians' Reports - General Correspondence regarding these Monthly Reports, 1960 (Box 69)
    - Kraenzel, Carl F. - Community Development - Activities in Iran, 1960 June (Box 69)
    - Iran - Reports - Carl F. Kraenzel - NEF Program Goals & Problems in Iran, 1960 (Box 69)
    - Iran Reports - Carl F. Kraenzel - Terminal Report for Master Contract, 1960 May (Box 69)
    - Iran - Fuller, Wm. - Termination Report, 1964 July (Box 69)
    - Fuller, Wm. A. - Field Trip Report (report on trip to Dezfool & Ahwa), 1961 December (Box 69)
    - Iran - Reports - Bell, T. - Terminal Report, 1964 (Box 69)
    - Terminal Report - Carl Kraenzel - Report - Area Director, 1961 July (Box 69)
    - Contract Specifications Bill of Quantitites - Boy's Club, 1967-1968 (Box 69)
    - Rural Resources Development Program for Jordan -Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
    - Terminal Report of the Community Development Pilot Demonstration inJordan, 1956-1960 (Box 69)
    - Rural Resources Development Program for Jordan Fifth Annual Report, 1964 (Box 69)
    - Balka - Wadi Seer Village Extension Project, 1974 (Box 69)
    - Rural Resources Development Program for Jordan Fourteenth Annual Report, 1973 (Box 69)
    - Rural Resources Development Program for Jordan Fourteenth Annual Report, 1974 (Box 66)
    - "JASH" Self-Help Program in Jordan - Progress Report, 1968 March (Box 69)
    - Boys Club Activities in Jordan - Annual Report, 1967 (Box 69)
    - Rural Resources Development Program for Jordan Eighth Annual Report, 1967 (Box 69)
    - Rural Resources Development Program for Jordan Sixth Annual Report, 1965 (Box 69)
    - Terminal Report of the Community Demonstration in Jordan, 1956-1960 (Box 69)
    - Jordan - Garden Club Project (Designated Area Tree Planting) (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Shami Goat Program by Cecil Blunn, 1974 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - NEF House Inventory, 1974-1976 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Hanna Khouri, 1971-1979 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Lebanon Youth Club Survey, 1971 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Ralph Mendenhall - Area Director, 1969-1972 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Misc. Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Melkon Markarian Fund, 1970-1975 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Misc. Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Misc. Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Negatives & Pictures, 1968-1978 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Nurse for Lebanon, 1977 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Olive Tree Problem (VITA), 1973-1975 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Pamphlets, Catalogue etc., 1968-1976 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Personnel - Finance - advance, severance, etc., 1970-1978 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Project "Asurua" (Tafila), 1968-1979 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Poultry Project Karma, 1968-1971 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Proposed Projects, 1961-1973 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Purchasing, Shipments & Supplies, 1964-1979 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Rabbit Production Program, 1977-1978 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Scholarships, 1960-1974 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Visitors, 1962-1978 (Box 70)
    - J.F.M. Carlier (Horticulturist) Final Report Jordan, 1979 February, September (Box 70)
    - "JASH" Self-Help Program in Jordan - Progress Report, 1968 March (Box 70)
    - "JASH" Self-Help" Program in Jordan - Annual Progress Report, 1968 (Box 70)
    - "JASH" Self-Help Program in Jordan - Progress Report, 1967 April (Box 70)
    - "JASH" Self-Help Program in Jordan - Annual Progress Report, 1969 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Balka Rural District Program, 1969 (Box 70)
    - Bees, 1968-1970 (Box 70)
    - Additional copy of Jordan's Monthly Reprot. Also Dooley's Monthly Report., 1961 June (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Boy's Club Annual Report, 1970 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Boys' Club Annual Report, 1969 (Box 70)
      - Photos, 2016:FA406:016 (Folder SF16)
    - Jordan - Boys' Club Annual Report, 1968 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Boys' Club Annual Report, 1967 (Box 70)
    - Annual Report - Jordan - Amman Youth Club Activities, 1964 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Calf Feeding Progress Report, 1971 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Reports - Raymond Abdul Massih - Director - Amman Urban Youth Training Center, 1960 (Box 70)
    - Final Report - Industrial Solicitation, 1962 (Box 70)
    - Preliminary Report - Industrial Solicitation, 1962 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Annual Reports - Cecil Blunn, 1973 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - "JASH" Annual Report, 1969 (Box 70)
    - Jordan "JASH" Annual Report, 1968 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - "JASH" Annual Report, 1967 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - JASH Reports - Annual, 1965-1966 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - JASH & Karak Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1979 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1978 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1977 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1976 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1975 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1974 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Report, 1973 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1972 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1967 (Box 70)
    - Jordan - Annual Report on Co-Operative Development, 1963-1964 (Box 71)
    - Combined Supplement for the Second Annual Report of NEF Consultants concerning the Development of Rezaiyeh Agricultural College, 1971-1977 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1966 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1965 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1964 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Monthly Reports, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Monthly Report, 1962 January - December (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Monthly Individual Reports, 1961 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Monthly Individual Reports, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Technicians' Monthly Report - General Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Delmar H. Dooley - Area Director - Monthly Progress Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Reveiw of NEF Program in Jordan by Janes Johnson, 1968 December (Box 71)
    - Fifth Annual Report - Nursery Stock & Distribution Project - Tafila, Jordan, 1975 (Box 71)
      - Photos, 2016:FA406:017 (Folder SF17)
    - Fifteenth Annual Report - Jordan - Rural Resources Development Program, 1974 (Box 71)
    - Fourth Annual Report - Jordan - Nursery Stock Production & Distribution Project (Tafila), 1974 (Box 71)
    - 1st Annual Report - Jordan - Nursery Stock Production & Distribution Project (Tafila), 970 (Box 71)
    - Progress Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1962 July 1 - December 31 (Box 71)
    - Progress Report - Dooley-Wood Progress Report, 1961 January 31 - May (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Report - Informational Data Concerning Financial Support by E. Howard, 1962 (Box 71)
      - Photos, 2016:FA406:018 (Folder SF18)
    - Report - Jordan Pictorial Report, 1964 January - June (Box 71)
    - 16th Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1975 (Box 71)
      - Photos, 2016:FA406:019 (Folder SF19)
    - 12th Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1971 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Annual Report - R. Mendenhall Village Agriculture Development, 1970 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - 10th Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1969 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - 9th Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1968 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - 8th Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1967 (Box 71)
    - 7th Annual Report - Rural resources Developoment Program, 1966 (Box 71)
    - 6th Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Progress, 1965 (Box 71)
    - Fifth Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1964 (Box 71)
    - Fourth Annual Report - Rural Resources Development Program, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Budget Report - Summary of funds recieved and exped. for Jordan RRDP, 1959 July 1 - 1964 February 29 (Box 71)
    - Annual Report for NEF/J - RRDP & Boys Club, 1962 July 1 - 1963 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Budget Report - Report of Funds Received & Expended, 1961 December 31 - 1962 (Box 71)
    - Second Annual Report - 1961 Rural Resources Development Program Emory M. Howard - Area Director (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Annual Report - Emory Howard - Area Director, 1962 (Box 71)
      - Illustrated Report - NEF Activities in Jordan, 2016:FA406:021 (Folder SF21)
    - Terminal Report - Dooley, Delmar J., 1959 September - 1961 August (Box 71)
    - Annual Report - Jordan - Rural Development Program, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Terminal Reports, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Wasp Control Program (Box 71)
    - Jordan - "Amman Urban Youth Training Center", 1959 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Amman Urban Youth Training Center, 1965 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Amman Urban Youth Training Center, 1960-1963 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Asphalt Mulch, 1962 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Artificial Insemination Program, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Bilharzia, 1964 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Budgets - Fiscal Yar, 1967-1968 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Cars, 1964-1969 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Community Development &Contract, 1961 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Contract, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Contract - Overhead Adjustments, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Contract - General Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 71)
    - Jericho Rehabilitation Center, 1961 (Box 71)
    - Jordan - Jericho Rehabilitation Project (blue prints), 1961-1963 (Box 71)
      - Proposed Workshops at the Social Welfare Centre Jericho Bluprint, 2016:FA406:022 (Folder SF22)
    - Jericho - Information on the Operation of UNRWA in the Jericho Area, 1964 (Box 71)
    - Jash & Karak - Jordan - Misereor, 1962 (Box 72)
    - Jash & Karak - Jordan - Catholic Near East Welfare, 1962 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Jash & Karak, 1964 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Jash Proposal & Amendment, 1964 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Jash & Karak, 1962-1963 (Box 72)
    - Jash Project Presentation Folder to Monsignor Ryan, New York, 1962 September (Box 72)
    - King's Dinner - All correspondence re: King Hussein's dinner, 1964 April 16 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - "NEED", 1968 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Office (Inventory), 1960-1968 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Tree & Vine Project, 1961-1968 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Rural Resources Development Fund, 1961-1963 (Box 72)
    - Summary Report - Rural Resources Development Program (First Year Operation), 1961 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Rural Resources Development Fund, 1960 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Rural Resources Development Fund, 1959 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - USOM/Jordan, 1960 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - USOM - c/o American Embassy, 1957 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Workmen's Compensation Insurance, 1960-1966 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - World Friendship Inc., (Dr. Parr), 1960 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Reports - A Study of Community Development Opportunities in Jordan, including Community Loans. Prepared for USOM/Jordan, 1954 December (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Annual Progress Reports, 1958 June (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Monthly Progress Reports, 1958, 1959 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Conn Price - Community Development Specialist, 1958 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Report - Cooperative Work on Agricultural Projects between the Ministry of Agriculture and NEF, 1964 (Box 72)
    - Jordan - Rural Resources Development Fund, 1964 (Box 72)
    - Trans - Jordanian (Box 72)
    - Jordan Contracts, 1955-1958 (Box 72)
      - Jordan - Contract signed, 1955 November 14 (Box 72)
      - Jodan - Contract, 1955 (Box 72)
      - Jordan Contract Amendment, 1956 November 13 (Box 72)
      - Jordan - Financial Reports to Washington (Box 72)
      - Jordan Contract - New, 1958 July 1 (Box 72)
      - New Jordan Contract - Letters of Commitment, 1958 July 1 (Box 72)
      - New Jordan Contract - Preliminary Draft, 1958 July 1 (Box 72)
      - Jordan - Correspondence, Discussions on Contract (Box 72)
      - Jordan - First Draft Contract (Box 72)
      - Jordan, Work Plans, Budget, PPA's (Box 72)
    - New Jordan Contract, 1958 (Box 72)
      - New Jordan Contract Amendments (Box 72)
      - Legal File #120A - Jordan Labor Laws (Box 72)
      - New Jordan Contract - Personnel Matters (Box 72)
      - Jordan Contract - Personnel Matters (Box 72)
    - Agrarian Development Contract FOA and NET - Personnel, 1955-1956 (Box 73)
      - FOA Agrarian Development Contract (Box 73)
      - Foreign Operation Administration (Box 73)
      - Iran - Agrarian Terminal Reports, 1956 (Box 73)
      - Iran - Agrarian Financial Statements (Box 73)
      - Iran - FOA Agrarian Development, 1955 (Box 73)
      - Agrarin Financial Statements (Box 73)
      - FOA Agrarian Development Contract (Box 73)
      - Agrarian Contract Correspondence (Box 73)
      - FOA Agrarian Development Contract (Box 73)
      - Mr. Crowthers Washington Folder (Box 73)
    - Cash Receipts Register, 1986 July 1 - December 31 (Box 73)
    - Cash Receipts Register, 1986 January 1 - June 31 (Box 73)
    - Cash Receipts Register, 1987 July 1 - 1988 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Cash Receipts Register, 1985 December 31 - July 1 (Box 73)
    - Cash Receipts Register, 1985 January 1 - June 30 (Box 73)
    - Original Cash Receipts Registers, 1988 July 1 - December 31 (Box 73)
    - Cash Receipts Register, 1987 January 1 - June 30 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Misc. Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 73)
    - Ghana Contract, 1958-1959 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Beers, 1960-1961 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Budget (see also Ghana - Finance), 1958 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Community Development, 1958 (Box 73)
    - Ghana Clippings (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Contract - Government & Contract (Duplicate letters), 1958 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Contract - Extensions - Amendments, 1958 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Contract - Home Leave Interpretation, 1959-1960 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Contract - Overhead Adjustment, 1960 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Contract - Personnel - Mission Approval, Leave, Salary Increases & Step Increases, 1959 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Mr. Peter du Sautory, 1958 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Employees Benefit Fund Statements, 1960-1961 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Government, 1959 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Government, 1958 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Government, 1957 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Hayden, 1958 January - June (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Holiday Schedule, 1960 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Housing Project, 1960 (Box 73)
    - Ghana - Smokeless Stove, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana -Howard, 1959 January - June (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Howard, 1958 July - December (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Howard, 1958 April - June (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Howard, 1958 January - March (Box 74)
    - Ghana - I.C.A., 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Mann, 1959 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Mann, 1958 January - March (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Office, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Personnel - Baggage Problems, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Personnel - Clearances, Leave for Personnel, Termination of Employment, 1961 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Personnel - Clearances, Leave for Personnel, etc., Termination of Employment, 1959-1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Program & Policy, 1959 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Program & Policy, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Program & Policy, 1957 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Publicity and Promotion, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Publicity & "Visiting Firemen" (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1961 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Shipment & Supplies - Purchasing, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - American Technicians' Reports General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Monthly Narrative Reports to Director of Social Welfare & USOM/Ghana, 1959 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Mason Beers - Area Director (Monthly Individual Reports), 1961 January (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Mason Beers - Area Director, 1960 August - December (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Lyle J. Hayden Overseas Program Director, 1960-1961 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Emory Howard - Area Director, 1959-1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Emory Howard - Area Director, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Thomas G. Hughes - Engineer, 1959-1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Jack W. Kulp - Engineer, 1958-1959 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - William Mann, Jr., Engineer, 1958-1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - William Mann ("The Pramkese Re-planning Scheme" by Okore Akrasi Agyemang) submitted by William Mann (Box 74)
    - Ghana - William Mann, Jr., "Replanning & lay-out" by S. Adarkwa-Addae, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Walter Murphy - Engineer, 1958-1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Philip R. Ourada - Engineer, 1961 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Pictorial Reports, 1961 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Allan L. Pitcher - Engineer, 1958-1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Dala Reeves, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Semi-Annual Performance Reports to Director of Social Welfare & USOM/Ghana, 1960-1961 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Terminal Report - Allan Pitcher, 1961 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Reports - Donald J. Terp, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - USOM & ICA, 1959 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - USOM & ICA, 1958 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Village Work, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Terminal Report - Volta Region - Ghana - Hiram Andrews, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Water & Sanitation, 1956 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Woman's Welfare Program, 1959 (Box 74)
    - Ghana - Workmen's Compensation Insurance, 1960 (Box 74)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1956-1960 (Box 74)
    - New Countries - Brazil (Material Mr. Wisdom left), 1963 (Box 74)
    - Rural Life Conference, Salonica, Greece, 1932 March 12-21 (Box 74)
    - Public Health, Medicine & Sanitation in Greece (Before the Axis Occupation) by Alice G. Carr, 1942 December (Box 74)
    - Athens Area Financial report, 1939 January (Box 74)
    - Agriculture in Macedonia & Thrace July 1952 by Charles A. Wright, Field Representative, 1952 July (Box 74)
    - Foreign Director's Report Summer Months, 1942 (Box 74)
    - Livestock Improvement Program for Greece, Athens, 1947 September (Box 74)
    - Foreign Director's Report, 1945 Spring (Box 74)
    - Rehabilitation of the Crippled & Injured in Greece and the Balkans, 1944 April 14 (Box 74)
    - The First Essentials in Restoring the War Disabled by Bell Greve, 1943 August (Box 70)
    - A Demonstration Plan for the Rehabilitation of the War Injured by Bell Greve, 1942 December (Box 75)
    - Final Report Livestock Improvement Program in Greece, 1940-1944 (Box 75)
    - A Tentative Plan for Livestock Improvement in Post War Greece by C.S. Stephanides, 1942 June 5 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Supplies Inventories, 1931 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial NEF Report, 1931 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial NEI Report, 1931 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial NEI Report, 1932 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial NEF Report, 1932 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial NEI Report, 1933 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial Report/New York A-1160, 1933 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial NEF Report/A-1116, 1933 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial NEI Report/ New York A-1665, 1934 December 31 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York A-1417, 1934 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial NEI Report/ New York A-1514, 1934 April - June 15 (Box 75)
    - Index, 1934-1937 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York A- 2132, 1937 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York A-2375, 1937 January 1 - December 31 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report, 1936 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5469, 1938 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial NEI Report, 1931 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial NEF Reports, 1931 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial NEF Reports, 1930 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report, 1933 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York A-1782, 1935 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York A-1588, 1934 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report, 1936 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report, 1935 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York A-1655, 1935 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Financial Report, 1936 February 11 - December 31 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York A-2311, 1937 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5544, 1939 February (Box 75)
    - Athens Industries Financial Report/ New York A-2693, 1938 January 16 - 1939 December 31 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report, 1939 March (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report New York C-5625, 1939 April (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5646, 1939 May (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5695, 1939 June (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5836, 1939 August (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C- 5898, 1939 October (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5937, 1939 November (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Equipment & Supplies Inventories, 1935 December 31 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Equipment Inventories, 1936 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5999, 1939 December (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Equipment Inventories, 1937 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Grecian Area Equipment & Supply Inventories, 1937 December 31 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5747, 1939 July (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5860, 1939 September (Box 75)
    - Atehns Area Equipment & Supplies Inventories, 1939 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Grecian Area Equipment Inventories, 1939 December 31 (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, Greece - Financial, 1932-1940 (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, Greece - Financial, 1940-1944 (Box 75)
    - H.B. Allen - Office Correspondence (B), 1939 (Box 75)
    - H.B. Allen - Office Correspondence (A), 1939 (Box 75)
    - H.B. Allen - Office Corresondence, 1940 (Box 75)
    - Docket Disbursement Committee Meeting, 1933 June 29 (Box 75)
    - Disbursement Committee Meeting, 1934 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1937 February 15 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1938 February 8 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1939 May 9 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1940 April 2 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1941 June 10 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1942 May 14 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1943 May 19 (Box 75)
    - NER - Disbursement Com., 1944 May 13 (Box 75)
    - Athens Area Supply & Equipment Inventories, 1933 December 31 (Box 76)
    - Biographies of several of the Macedonian Agriculturists / Case Histories of farmers / Letters to magazine: The American Agriculturieset, 1930-1935 (Box 76)
    - Supplementary Statements for Executive Committee Meeting, 1933 February 24 (Box 76)
    - Supplementary Statements for Executive Committee Meeting, 1931 December 10 (Box 76)
    - Disbursement Committee Meeting, 1932 (Box 76)
    - Analysis of Macedonian Program, 1932 (Box 76)
    - Outline of Macedonian Program, 1933 (Box 76)
    - Athens Area Supply & Equipment Inventories, 1934 (Box 76)
    - Inventories of NEF Equipment & Supply, 1934 June 30 (Box 76)
    - Supplement Statements Executive Committee Meeting, 1933 December 28 (Box 76)
    - Athens Area Financial Report/ New York C-5406, 1938 June (Box 76)
    - Agenda - Near East Institutes Committee, 1929 January 23 (Box 76)
    - Agenda - Near East institutes Committee, 1929 January 23 (Box 76)
    - Laird Archer: Office Correspondence, 1938 (Box 76)